bodyparts.biz 2009-04-13

# Close up Big Tits | Close up Tits Free | Natural Tits

Flash Productions Privacy Policy  

Your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy governs your use of this website, BodyParts.biz.

The following information describes how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us, while accessing and using our site. By accessing and using our site, you signify your acceptance to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our site. 

Information Collection/Use   
In certain areas of the site, we may request that you provide us with personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, birth date, opinions and preferences. We log all users’ information when signing onto or using this site, including but not limited to IP address, URL of the web page user was on before visiting this site, user's browser version, user's registration forms, surveys, cookie data and communications transmitted through applications on the site. We reserve the right to use this information to find ways to improve sales to members, to increase the users experience accordingly, or to formulate statistical models to accomplish our goals through surveys. We are the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others without your express consent. 

We will use cookies to track affiliate sales and referring URL's. In the future, we may use cookies to personalize services for members, to track browsers, to identify the most popular areas of our site and to determine the effectiveness of our promotional activities. Please note that some of our business partners may also use cookies on our sites, however, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

Sharing   
Financial Data will only be shared with third party processors, as is necessary to initiate and complete any orders placed by your account. We may use “cookies” and demographic information to better your experience on this site. Aggregate, non-individual membership demographic information may be shared with third parties, with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship, who may offer products or services we believe you might be interested in. We may also share the aggregate demographic information with third parties for the purposes of analyzing usage data, maintaining servers and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving our service and the site. 

Your name, physical address, phone number and password are considered confidential. However, all information you provide to us may be shared as necessary to comply with applicable law, or to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system. 

We do not currently sell or otherwise make available personally identifiable information about our users to third parties. Nevertheless, we reserve the right to make such information available to third parties in the future, in order to enhance and personalize our products and services to benefit users, or in the case of bankruptcy, sale of an asset, business or division, a merger or acquisition, or similar change of ownership.   

Your email address will be used by us to contact you when we have special offers or other important information. This may include, without limitation, new services, information relating to your account and your subscription to this site. We may send you emails prior to and after you have terminated your membership, until such time as you advise us, in accordance with the procedures explained below, that you no longer wish to receive email from us and/or from third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship. We may share your email address with other parties, with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship with, for the purposes of sending you special advertisements or promotions. If you no longer wish to receive emails from us or from such third parties, please email us and we will be glad to remove you. 

We and our advertising partners fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act. All emails from us and our advertising partners will always, among other required disclosures, have a place for you to opt out of receipt of further email correspondence. Please note we will never send you an email directly or through our marketing partners without your consent.

Your Responsibility  
We process credit card transactions via industry standard encryption through third party processors, which use your information only for that purpose. Financial data is considered private information and will not be shared by us with third parties, except with your authorization and as necessary to carry out orders placed by you with the understanding that such transaction (s) may be subject to the rules and policies of such third party. Financial or other data provided by you to any companies or websites advertising on this site or in response to emails sent to you by those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. Any information provided by you to a third party and any transaction with such third party, is subject to that party’s terms and conditions and privacy policy. 

Advertisements  
We may utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our services and goods and/or services offered by third parties. Either we or our advertising agencies may use cookies and/or “action tags” to measure advertising effectiveness on an “anonymous basis”. Some emails from us may contain advertisements from companies unrelated to our site. Should you elect to visit any such advertiser’s website, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about applicable terms and conditions or privacy policies for such advertisers’ websites. If you choose to make any purchases on such sites or accept any offers from such companies, we may provide your information, including financial data, to the advertiser as necessary to your request. Finally, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about the privacy policies or terms and conditions of advertisements appearing anywhere on our service, whether through our website or emails. This is regardless of whether or not there may be any mentions of or references to our site on such advertisers’ website (s). 

Law Enforcement   
We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants and others seeking information about our end users, to the extent required by applicable law, such as: compliance with discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders and writs. 

Links   
These sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave this site, they should read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. 

Security   
We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. We do not keep sensitive billing information on our local servers. The billing processors will keep this information. We retain all users' information in a secure database, indefinitely. 

Adults Only   
This is an “adults only” service. We will suspend or terminate any accounts which we believe are being used by anyone under the age of eighteen (18) years old or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you view this site. Additionally, we reserve the right to report such person to the proper authorities along with all information provided to us by or with respect to such person. 

Choice   
From time to time, we may send our users e-mails, e-mail newsletters, site news updates, or other notices regarding new services, promotions, or other information which may be of general interest. Users who no longer wish to receive materials from us may discontinue receiving these communications by choosing a "opt out" option or by contacting us. We will comply with all requests for removal. 

Changes   
We may make changes to this privacy policy at any time. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of such changes. Instead, it is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. Changes to the privacy policy will be effective upon posting. We recommend that you read this Privacy Policy carefully and consult it regularly. If you continue to access or use our site after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you signify your acceptance to the changes in our Privacy Policy. 

If we decide to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated in the Privacy Policy at the time that such information was collected, we will attempt to notify you of such changes. You agree that if we send you an e-mail, to the e-mail address reflected in our records, such e-mail will constitute acceptable notice to you of the change in our policy. The notice will provide you with an opportunity to "opt-out", so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is different from that described at the time you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions provided to you in the notice, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the notice. If we have no e-mail address for you, or if we do not have a current e-mail address for you, then you agree that adequate notice of the change in our policy will be effected by posting such a change onto our Privacy Policy, which shall also disclose information about how you may “opt-out" so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is materially different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions posted within the time period specified, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information as described in the posted notice. 

Contact Information   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you otherwise need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable information, please contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide your name, mailing address, telephone number and e-mail address so we can service you quicker. Please send your e-mail to: support@BodyParts.biz. 

© Flash Productions, LLC (2008)
